https://mjf.ie/cookie-policy/

Privacy & Cookie Policy
This Privacy and Cookies Policy refers to the website, www.mjf.ie. It sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.
Please read the following carefully. Entering into this Website indicates that the user (either “user” or “you”) has reviewed this Privacy Policy and has agreed to be bound by it. If you do not agree to these terms, we ask you to desist from visiting this website immediately.
What information do we collect?
We fully respect your right to privacy in relation to your interactions with the website and endeavour to guarantee to be transparent as to what information we will collect and how we will use your information. Information in relation to personal data collected by Irish entities is available on www.dataprotection.ie, the website of the Irish Data Protection Commissioner.
How do we collect information from you?
IP Addresses
We collect IP addresses from visitors to our website (an IP address is a number that can uniquely identify a specific computer or other network device on the internet). This allows us to collect statistics in relation to the number and geographic location of visitors to our site. We analyse this data for marketing purposes.
Cookies
Our website uses cookies to give you the best online browsing experience.  By choosing to continue on our site, we’ll assume that you are happy with our cookie policy.To provide you with the best possible online browsing experience, we use cookies, small pieces of data which are sent from our website and stored on your computer’s web browser.  Many of these cookies are essential pieces of code, without which our website would not function correctly.  However, these cookies never store any piece of identifiable information about our website visitors.  We are committed to respecting and protecting your online identity in line with Irish and EU law.There are different types of cookies used on our site as follows:
Session Cookies
Session cookies contribute to a faster browsing experience by tracking your movement through the site so are not asked to re-process each new page that you visit.  Session cookies are not stored on your computer and as the name suggests, expire once your browser session is closed.
Double Click Cookies
These cookies are used by our online advertising partners and are used to serve internet ads that we run on other sites.
Google Analytics Cookies
Google Analytics cookies allow us to track and record anonymous browsing activity on our website.  This data gives us information such as number of visitors to the site, number of pages visited and the length of time spent on each page.  This data is completely anonymous and cannot be traced back to an individual.  It allows us to better tailor our website content for our visitors and to make it an even more positive experience when browsing our online presence.
By continuing to our website, you are granting us permission to use cookies as part of your browsing experience.
However, you can block any cookies from any website through the options setting on your browser settings.
Registration process
If users wish to access certain market research reports and other valuable documentation, they are requested to sign up.  To register to access this documentation, we collect information such as name, job title, company name, email address and telephone number. We may also ask for other information which helps to personalise our communications to you. You may unsubscribe at any time from communications with us by emailing marketing@mjf.ie . All email communications also includes an ‘unsubscribe’ option in line with good industry practice.
How do we use the information we collect?
We collect information to allow us personalise your experience and interactions with our company. We may also use your data to provide you with information about goods and services, that we feel might be of interest to you, based on previous online interactions with our organisation. By accepting this privacy and cookie policy, you are granting us permission to do so.
How do we protect your personal information?
We do our utmost to protect your information throught the use of secure, robust hardware ad software technologies.   However, this website includes cookies from third parties as described above and these organisations have their own privacy policies. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for the privacy practices of such third party websites and your use of such websites is at your own risk.
Who do we share data with?
We will not disclose your information to any third parties. But we may use your data to contact you in relation to goods and/or services which we feel may be of interest to you. You may unsubscribe from these communications at any time.
Where do we store your personal data?
The data that we collect from you is stored within the Republic of Ireland. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers and we have rigorous security policies in place to ensure that your data is protected at all times.
However, we acknowledge that the movement of data across the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time, so you may wish to check it each time you submit personal information to the Website. The date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page. If you do not agree to these changes, please do not continue to use this website to submit personal information. If material changes are made to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by placing a prominent notice on the Website.
Consent
By accessing services offered by us, you consent to the collection and use of this information by us as outlined in this Privacy Policy. By providing any personal information to us, you fully understand and clearly consent to such use and transfers as set out in this Privacy Policy.
News & Events Categories
Blog
Case Studies
Events
Jobs
News
News & Events
Webinars
April 2005
About MJ Flood Technology is a leading provider of total ICT solutions and supporting services across Ireland and the UK. We are proud to be Irelands leading certified partner of Cisco, HP and Microsoft.
Read More »
Our SolutionsManaged Tablet
IT Infrastructure
Virtualisation
Unified Communications
Mobility
Information Security & Protection
Collaboration
Interactive Display Technology
Internet of Things
Big Data
Other MJ Flood Divisions Managed Print Services
Office Interiors
Interior Contracting
Office Supplies
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read Privacy PolicyPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
Scroll to top
